Guide to the Delmer Daves Papers, 1930-1965
Department of Special Collections
- Susan Slade
  - American Magazine - tearsheet- the Sin of Susan Slade- original story by Doris Hume., 11/54; Ca. 20 pgs. Printed. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - American Magazine., 11/54 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Lovers Must Learn (WB), 1939-1961
  - History of Original SP of Lovers Must Learn from 1939 with changes referred by Breen office., ND (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - TLC JIB to David Loew re: censors' comments., 4/26/39; 3 pgs.
  - TLC JIB to David Loew re: script with changes now acceptable., 4/28/39
  - TLC DD to JIB re: explanation of changes of script., ND
  - TLC David L. Loew to Raymond Crossett re: no more interest in script., 5/1/39
  - TLC DD to Loew re: lawsuit., 5/2/39
  - TLC Irving Fineman to Raymond Crossett re: doesn't want lawsuit., 5/4/39
  - TLS Alvin M. Asher (for Loeb and Loeb Law Firm) to DD re: consideration of suit., 5/5/39
  - TLC John McCormick to Loew re: comments on Loew's reneging and support of suit., 5/8/39; 2 pgs.
  - TLS Harry Sokolov to McCormick re: payment for handling suit., 5/9/39
  - TLS A. M. Asher to DD re: enclosing copy of letter from Loew., 5/10/39
  - TLC Loew to McCormick re: explanation of decision., 5/10/39
  - TLS McCormick to DD re: enclosing #10 above., 5/10/39; 8vo.
  - TLC DD to Loew re: explanation of minor changes reqauired by JIB., 5/13/39
  - TLC Loew to DD re: reconfirming decision to withdraw., 5/15/39
  - TLC DD to Loew re: informing of decision to prosecute., 5/31/39
  - TLS A. M. Asher to DD re: denies above #15., 6/19/39
  - Synopsis of Lovers Must Learn, 9/18/39; 16 pgs. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Synopsis of censored adaptations of Lovers Must Learn by DD and Irving Fineman. M., 1939; 21 pgs. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Number of changes suggested by JIB listed by pg. number., ND
  - Kstimating script with commentaries by Fineman and reactions by DD with PpNAD., 7/17/61; 138 pgs. M. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - --- Same as #19 with cnages dated 7/28/61 and 8/2/61. (Box 57, Folder 9,10)
    9 - script
    10 - changes
  - 4th draft SP by DD with OPpNAD., ND; 122 pgs. (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - 2nd and 3rd drafts with changes and FPNAD. M., 1954; 126 pgs. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - 4th Rev. draft-Italian version with PNAD., ND; 132 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - 4th draft-French Version., ND; 132 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Lovers Must Learn - notes re; fall of 1939, war, synopsis, with script., ND; 118 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Lovers Must Learn., ND; 118 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - SP with FPpNAD., 3/23/39; 111 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Rome Adventure (retitled), 1961
  - Final Script with cutting notes, pD., 9/7/61; 135 pgs. M.
  - Synopsis of Rome Adventure. M., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Production notes. M., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Estimating script with revisions. M, 7/17/61; 138 pgs. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Complete shooting script with notes, diagrams, FPpNAD and sketches, 9/7/61; (ca. 130 pgs., 8/pg., 1 3/4" × 2 1/2"). (Box 59, Folder 1,2)
    1 to p. 116
    2 p. 117 on
  - Early location research; inventory of 35 mm. color slides, and [movement] in Italy, June, 1961., ND; 8vo. 53 slides. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Location notes from Italy-bound notebook., ND; 3 3/4" C 5 1/2". (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Breakdown of sequences for location shooting. M., ND; 66 pgs. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Call sheets and shooting schedules., 9/17/61-9/28/61; Legal. M. 66 pgs. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Staff and cast list with addresses and telephone numbers., 9/29/61+10/9/61 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Folder 1
  - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re: enclosing tape report transcript from DD in Italy., 8/24/61; 8vo. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Transcript for tape #1. C., 8/23/61; 22 pgs.
  - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re: transcript #2., 8/25/61; 8vo. C.
  - Transcript #2. C., 8/16/61; 19 pgs.
  - Transcript #3. C., 8/17/61; 19 pgs.
  - Transcript #4. C., 8/24/61; 15 pgs.
  - Memo-give copy of transcript #5 to wardlobe., ND; 3" × 5"
  - Transcript #5. C., 8/27/61; 16 pgs.
  - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re: Transcript #6 C., 9/12/61; 8vo.
  - Transcript #6. C., 9/8/61; 18 pgs.
  - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re: Transcript #9. C., 10/3/61; 8vo.
  - Transcript #9. C., 9/8/61; 11 pgs.
  - IOC HHF to C. Greenlaw re: transcript #7. C., 9/14/61; 8vo.
  - Transcript #7. C., 9/7/61; 19 pgs.
  - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re:transcript #8. C., 9/21/61; 8vo.
  - Transcript #8. C., 9/15/61; 21 pgs.
- Folder #2
  - Production correspondence between International Film Service, Rome (a European film for handling American filming abroad), director of service, Guy Longo and C. Greenlaw in Calif., G. L. Blattner in England and DD directing and producing. TLS 5/31/61-11/27/61-31 pieces., --- (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Cables to DD from WB staff in Calif. re: production and problems., 6/6/61-11/61; 23 pieces. 6 3/4" × 8 1/2". (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - 2 original cable drafts, DD to William Orr re: production aspects and problems., ND (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Telegram WB to DD re: received annual Laurel Award., 8/2/61; 8vo, 3 pgs. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - TLC DD to G. L. Blattner re: production., 7/12/61
  - TLC DD to Irving Fineman re: script changes and comments., 7/19/61
  - TLC G. L. Blattner to Wm. Orr re: production information., 7/20/61; 8 pgs.
  - TLC G. L. Blattner to W. Orr re: screen credits for International Film Service., 7/21/61
  - TLC G. Shurlock to JAW re: censors' comments., 7/21/61; 3 pgs.
  - IOC C. Greenlaw to all dept.:re: budget meeting. M., 7/27/61
  - TLS G. L. Blattner to DD re: casting, credits and equipment for film., 8/2/61; 2 pgs.
  - IOC DD to C. Greenlaw re: filming and sound., 8/3/61
  - TLS Roger Dollarhide to HF re: enclosing [UNK] Learn., 8/3/61; 2 pgs.
  - TLS C. Greenlaw to DD re: production information and details., 8/7/61
  - TNS Michael DAves (son) to HF re: message for DD., 8/7/61; 3 in. × 5 in.
  - IOC-S HF to C. Greenlaw re: enclosing mail to be sent to DD., 8/7/61; 8vo.
  - IOC-S HF to DD re: putting ad in MP Exhibitor., 8/7/61
  - IOC Carl Milliken, Jr. to Roy Obringer re: clearance of proper names., 8/8/61
  - TLS Eugene Lerner to DD re: using Rossano Brazzi in film, with PN., 8/9/61
  - TLS V. Rollo to DD re: cooperation with ship scenes., 8/10/61
  - TLS C. Greenlaw to DD re: production matters and an enclosure., 8/11/61
  - TLC C. Greenlaw to Luongo re: technical production problems., 8/11/61
  - ALS Simon Mizrahi to DD re: arrangeing a meeting., 8/11/61
  - TLS G. L. Blattner to DD re: budget., 8/12/61
  - IOC-S HF to C. Greenlaw re: enclosing information of #31., 8/14/61
  - TLS Isadore Kessler to DD re: submitting music for film., 8/14/61
  - Verifax sheet music, ND; 10 1/4" × 26".
  - TLS Max Bercutt to DD re: publicity for Alitalia., 8/15/61
  - TLC G. L. Blattner to Parker Harris re: Insurance policy agreements., 8/16/61; 2 pgs.
  - Memo CF (?) to DD re: information., 8/17/61; 4" × 6".
  - TLS Gene Lerner to DD re: recommending Letitia Roman as actors., 8/17/61
  - TLS R. Dollarhide to DD re: wants to work his song into film., 8/17/61
  - TLS Phil Gersdorf to DD re: regrets can't do film with DD., 8/18/61
  - TLC G. Sharlock to JLW re: censorship., 8/21/61
  - TLS HF to DD re: 2nd request for ad, see #28., 8/21/61
  - TLS CF [?] to DD re: ad, see #45., 8/23/61
  - TLS Dick Lederer to DD re: trailer advertising., 8/24/61; 2 pgs.
  - TLS Gayne Rescher to DD re: filming on board ship., 8/29/61
  - TLS Helen Boll to Mrs. DD re: care of home business in DD's absence., 9/5/61
  - TLS Guy Gadbois to Mrs. DD re: personal financial business., 9/5/61
  - TLS C. Greenlaw to DD re: general business and Troy Donahue's overspending., 9/5/61; 2 pgs.
  - TLS William Orr to DD re: technical matters of production., 9/5/61; 3 pgs.
  - ALS K. Kuter to DD re: art production and set matters., 9/8/61; 3 pgs.
  - TLC G. Shurlock to JLW re: more censoring., 9/12/61; 2 pgs.
  - TLC J. C. Youngerman to Walter MacEwen re: co-assistant director credit granted., 11/17/61
  - TLC DD to Hector Santee re: reimbursement for equipment damaged en route or lost., 11/24/61
  - ALS Tom Bessinger to DD with envelope re: meeting in Tialy., 8/18/61; 8vo.
  - Telegram JW to DD and D. Greenlaw re: production., ND
  - A. draft for telegram to Bill Orr re: give Troy Donahue rest before shooting., ND
  - Draft to Louella[Parsons] from DD re: general news of production., ND
  - Draft of letter, DD to Hedda [Hopper] re: general news., ND
  - TN to DD re: Dollarhide wants part in film., ND
  - Verifax copy-verification of writing credits., 11/17/61
  - TLS? To D.D., 8/14/61; 2 pgs
  - Shooting schedule for 9/61 and 10/61 on location. M., 8/1/61; Legal. 9 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Rev. shooting schedule (original with PN)&transcribed copy). T. and C., 9/1/61; 9 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Locations schedule with PN., ND; 6 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Locations schedule. C., ND; 5 pgs.
  - Shooting schedule - working days out of days. C., ND (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 3rd draft-tentative Italian Lire costs-, 8/19/61; 2 copies. C. 7 pgs. each. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Shooting schedule for secondary roles with PpN., 8/9/61 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - p. - talent needed by local Italians on location., ND (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Wardrobe schedule., ND (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Travel units-cast and crew list with addresses and telephone numbers. M., 8/28/61; 8 1/2" × 13". (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - List of places to be dubbed. M., 12/12/61; 3 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Actor/actress selection list with PN. M., 7/10/61; 2 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Staff and cast lists with addresses and telephone numbers., 9/29/61
  - Miscellaenous notes, sketches, 2 calling cards., ND; ca. 20 odd sized pgs. Pp. (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Rome Adventure
  - Final script- Lovers Must Learn., 9/7/61; 135 pgs. M. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Folder 1
    - Record of work done by DD. C., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Exterior sets-list of Italian locations-original plus C. with PN., ND; 2 pgs. each. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Footage per scenes - 1st cut. C., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - IOC-S DD to Orr-Trilling-Ziegler-Blau re: cutting suggestins., 1/24/62; 2 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - IOC DD to Bill Orr re: updating film for preview., 12/20/60
    - IOC Obringer to Orr re: obtaining Marlon Brando's permission to use name inscript. C., 11/10/61; 8vo.
    - IOC-S DD to Bill Orr re: cutting and substituting scenes., 10/18/61
    - IOC-S Bill Orr to DD re: suggestins for minor changes., 12/18/61
    - IOC DD to C. Greenlaw re: filming equipment needed. C., 8/3/61 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Dubbing material for C. I. T. Guide. C., 12/12/61; 3 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Women's wardrobe plot. M., 7/24/61; 9 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Men's wardrobe plot. M., 7/24/61; 9 pgs.
    - IOC-S HF to print shop re: make 20 copies of trailer scene. Svo., 10/16/61 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Trailer scene. M., 10/16/61; 2 copies. 2 pgs. each.
    - Daily production and progress reports., 8/1/61-1/30/62; 53 pgs. C. Legal (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - IOC C. Greenlaw to Bill Orr re: progress reports., 10/4/61-11/9/61; 8vo. 27 pgs.
    - Shooting schedule for all WB productions M., 9/6/61-10/31/61; 12 pgs. both sides. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Call sheet for actors on location. M, 10/31/61-10/24/61; 13 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Folder 2
    - Cast and crew lists with addresses and telephone numbers. M. and T. with pA., 9/29/61 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Cast list with addresses and telephone numbers. M., 10/9/61
    - IOC Hoyt Bowers to C. Greenlaw-Bau-Hiatt-Schweibert re: screen test. C., 7/31/61 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Screen test for Prudence. M., ND; 3 pgs.
    - Screen test for Don. M., ND; 2 pgs.
    - Staff and crew list invited to party. C., 11/1/61; 2 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - IOC Hoyt Bowers to JLW-Orr-Trilling-Benson, C. Greenlaw-DD re: final list for acting credits., 10/10/61 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - List of actors, parts and addresses and telephone numbers., 10/9/61 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Biography of Troy Donahue. M, ND; 3 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Index to and breakdown of scenes. M., 7/24/61; 51 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Folder 3
    - Telegram JLW to DD re: pleased with film., 12/1/61; 3 3/4" × 8 1/2" (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - IOC-S Walter MacEwen to DD re: Bert Steiner as dialogue director., 9/26/61; 8vo.
    - Telephone messages and appointments taken by HF., 6/27/61-2/2/62; 8vo. 41 pgs. both sides. (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - List of interview requests., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - IOC-S Carl Combs to HF re: enclosure., 10/22/62; 8vo. (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - TLS Capt. J. F. Collins to WB re: wants information on movie., 8/22/62
    - Business correspondence to European personnel., --- (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - a. 11/2/61TLC DD to Luongo
      - b. 11/2/61TLC DD to G. L. Blattner
      - c. 7/18/61TCS HF to C. Greenlaw., 3" × 5".
      - d. 7/18/61TLC DD to Luongo., 2 pgs.
      - e. 7/12/61TLC DD to Luongo., 5 pgs.
      - f. 7/25/61TLC DD to Hugh Gigault, Italian Lines, 2 pgs.
      - g. 7/18/61TLC DD to Blattner
      - h. 7/19/61TLC DD to Irving Fineman
      - i. 7/20/61TLC DD to Luougo., 3 pgs.
    - TLS Gayne Rescher to DD re: getting film shots and enclosing 7 1/2" × 9" picture with idea for hidden camera., 7/7/61 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - TLS Joe Castor to DD re: advertising arrangement with North American Van Lines., 8/29/61
    - TCS HF to DD re: advertising copy for magazine., 8/23/61; 3" × 5". 2 pgs.
    - Delivery slip for roles of film., 8/4/61; 8vo.
    - IOC HF to DD re: taking out an ad in newspaper. C., 8/7/61
    - TLC HF to DD re: general news., 8/18/61
    - TLC HF to DD re: remember about answering ad request., 8/21/61
    - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re: enclosing letters for DD., 8/7/61; 8vo.
    - Copy of wire, WB to DD re: congratulations on Laurel award., 8/2/61
    - IOC HF to C. Greenlaw re: enclosing letter. C., 8/14/61; 8vo.
    - TLC V. Rollo to DD re: OK in using their ship., 8/10/61
    - TLS Bill Cooper to DD re: Handling his material as an agent., 2/8/61
    - TLS Frank Cooper to DD re: wants to make lunch appointment., 2/10/61
    - TLC HF to Frank Cooper re: apologies for misplacing #14 and #15 above for 5 months., 8/22/61
    - TLC Frank Cooper to HF re: acknowledge #16., 8/25/61
    - TLC Roger Dollarhide to DD re: meeting DD in Italy., 6/24/61
    - TLC HF to Dollarhide re: contact Guy Luongo., 7/11/61
    - TLS Dollarhide to HF re: acting in Rome., 7/28/61; 8vo.
    - TLC HF to Dollarhide re: lyrics submitted have been sent to DD 8/3/61. origional and 2 C. copies., 8/17/61; 3 pgs.
    - TLC DD to JW re: recommend Bert Steiner., 10/31/61
    - TLC DD to Henry Koster re: recommending Bert Steiner., 10/31/61
    - TLS Meta Rebenr to DD re: general regards and news., 6/23/61; 6" × 8 1/2". 2 pgs.
    - Requisition for stores. C., 7/25,31+12/8/61; 8vo.
  - Folder 4
    - 11 ALS and TLS (fan mail) requesting information on music theme from Rome Adventure with answer., --- (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - List of recordings of theme Al diLa by E. Pericoli., ND (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Biography of Emilio Pericoli. M., ND; 2 copies. 1 pg each.
    - List of cast and crew requests for songs and misc notes on recordings, etc., ND
  - Folder 5
    - 14 ALS and TLS fan mail answered by HF re: general information on picture, --- (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Sheet of research information on Lovers Must Learn, ND (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Note on European title., ND; 3" × 5".
  - Folder 6
    - 30 ALS and TLS-fan mail, answered. by HF, --- (Box 60, Folder 41)
- Mothers and Daughters Pt. I(Columbia), 1961
  - SP by DD based on novel by Evan Hunter. ca. 200 pgs. C. 1st draft with changes and notes dated 2/3/61. PpNAD, ND (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 2nd draft SP with PpNAD by Evan Hunter., 4/12/61; 170 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - 3rd draft SP, marked copy by Hunter., 4/21/61; 157 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - TLS Evan Hunter to DD with pN re: comments on script. C., 4/30/61; 4 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Report on Mothers and Daughters novel by DD. M., 2/27/61; 35 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 1st draft page outline-breakdown of novel with PN., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - AN and breakdown., ND; 37 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Notes on conference with Evan Hunter., 2/23/61; 5 pgs. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Notes on approaches, themes. etc., ND; 5 pgs.
  - Notes on discussion of 3rd draft, 4/26/61., ND; 2 pgs.
  - Good Housekeeping with excerpt from novel by Hunter-Amanda, 5/61 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Mothers and Daughters Pt. II
  - Pgs. 406 - 413 (from unknown magazine) with notes by Hunter., ND (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - 1st estimating draft with Hunter notes., 5/12/61; 161 pgs. M. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - TLS Hunter to DD re: comments on script., 5/16/61
  - Copy of original draft of novel Mothers and Daughters with FPpNAD, by Hunter., ND; 923 pgs. (Box 62, Folder 1-9)
- Seventeenth Summer (WB), 1962
  - Original novel by Maureen Daly cut and pasted on paper with margin notes and FPpNAD, ND; ca. 250 pgs. both sides. (Box 63, Folder 1,2)
  - Messages and appointments for 5 weeks during absence of DD., 2/5/62-3/10/62; 7 pgs both sides. 8vo. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - 3" × 5" card re: information and DD's activities., ND
  - Memo Ben to HR re: return novel when done., ND; 4 1/4" × 5 1/2".
  - IOC HF to Johnny O'Steen re: return of book Stencer's Mountain. C., 3/6/62; 8vo.
  - Scores requisition. C., 2/1/62; 8vo. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - 2 copies of cover of M. Daly novel with biography of authoress on it. Printed., ND (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Notes on characters to be cast., ND; 8vo. 5 pgs. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Page by page outline and breakdown of novel. P., ND; 2 pgs. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - 1st draft-breakdown, and notes on novel. T. with PpN., ND; 10 pgs.
  - Notes on Granville, Ohio., ND; Legal. 2 pgs. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - 1st 4 pages of script with pNAD., ND; Legal
  - 1st draft SP by DD with OPpNAD and T. foreword (1 pg.). M., ND; 111 pgs. (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Spencer's Mountain (WB), 1962
  - Complete shooting script-SP by DD from novel by Earl Hammer, Jr. with FPpNAD, diagrams, maps, add scene sketches, 6/11/62; (132 pgs., 8/pg., 1 1/2" × 3 3/8"). 132 pgs. both sides. M. (Box 63, Folder 10,11)
    10 to p. 70
    11 p. 70 on
  - Unmarked final script. M., 6/11/62; 132 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 1st draft SP with PNAD., ND; 135 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - a. synopsis-notes on people and places., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - b. outlines., 6 pgs.
  - c. galleys., 7 pgs.
  - d. original novel cut and pasted on paper with extensive PN by DD., ca. 120 pgs. both sides.
  - Estimating script. M., 4/17/62; 132 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Changes. M., 5/25/62; 123 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Estimating script with changes if 5/25/62. M., 5/25/62; 123 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Spencer's Mountain
  - Pp cutting notes for 20 reels., ND; Legal. 21 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Lyrics for hymns and songs., ND; 11 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Estimating budget. M., 6/27/62; 10" × 13". 11 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Index and breakdown for sequences with OPNAD. M., 6/14/62; 101 pgs. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Men's wardrobe plot. M., 6/15/62; 51 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Women's wardrobe plot. M., 6/15/62; 24 pgs.
  - 2 blue ink drawings of an interior of a log cabin., ND (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Comments an Hank's notes-description of specific seanes., ND; 3 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Research report-quarries in California., ND (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - IOC-S HF to DD re: miscellaneous office business., 6/29/62 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - IOC-S HF to DD re: more office business and news.*, 6/29/62
  - TLC DD to Harthon R. Bill re: production plans for location filming., 6/12/62; 1 pg. both sides.
  - Possible pre-production and post-production work. C., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Cast selection information and selection lists with PpNAD., ND; 2 copies. Legal. 4 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Pictures of interviewed actors with PpAN., ND; 15 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Casting suggestions and notes with FPN, ND.; 11 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - IOC HF to Ray Monroe re: gate passes for interviewees. C., 6/12/62
  - Hoyt Bowers to Greenlaw-Bau-Hiatt-Schweibert re: screen tests. M., 6/8/62
  - PpN on casting., NDN; 8 1/2" × 9 1/2". 8 pgs.
  - PpN on casting., ND; 3 pgs.
  - Pictures of possible actors., ND; 2 pgs.
  - Final staff and cast list with addresses, 6/22/62; [UNK] 4 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Cast list., 6/26/62; 2 pgs
  - Cast list., 6/18/62
  - Correction to cast list, 7/9/62
  - Cast and stop list. M., ND (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Travel scheduel with pN., ND; 2 pgs.
  - Bit list. M., ND; 3 pgs.
  - Call sheets and shooting schedule with WB set requirements., 7/27/62-8/16/62; ca. 100 pgs. both sides.
  - Complete production crossplot-purple ink mimeograph., 6/21/62; 2 pgs. 28" × 17". (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Locations and interiors-descriptions in continuity with PNAD., ND; 2 copies, 1 T. and 1 C.. 5 pgs. each. (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Possible pre-production and pos-production work., ND; 4 pgs.
  - Cast and crew living assignments in Jackson Hole, Wyo.. Purple ink Mimeograph., ND; 5 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Location notes., ND (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Addresses and Wyoming contacts. Both sides., ND (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - 12 odd sized P and blue print maps of Wyo. location., ND (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - P. Highway directions to West Yellowstone., ND (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Misc. P. notes. both sides., ND
  - Jackson Hole Guide re: article on Spencer's Mountain., 7/26/62 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - LA Examiner re: article on movie., 7/11/62 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Ad for Pink Garter Theater in Jackson Hole., ND (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Information sheet for writing credits., 8/10/62 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Telegram Jack Lederer to DD re: wardrobe problems., 6/25/62; 8vo. (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - [?] to DD re: answering congratulations. Telegram., 7/11/62; 8vo.
  - Lederer to Trilling-DD-Bercutt re: submitting film to European Film Festival., 1/28/63
  - Telegram Kelmenson to DD re:Film booked for Radio City., 1/28/63; 8vo.
  - Lederer to DD re: Same as c30., 1/30/63; 8vo.
  - Telegram DD to Lederer re: thanks., 1/30/63
  - Hyams to Lederer telegram: good reviews from Arthur Godfrey.', 2/12/63
  - IOC-S Victor Blau to Giles Kessel re: music for film., 6/19/62; 8vo.
  - Memo Max Bercutt to DD re: Godfrey review., ND
  - IOC-S Marie Level to DD re:thanks for invitation to premier., 5/29/63
  - IOC-S Fred Ponendel oo DD re: same as no. 30., 5/29/63
  - IOC-DD to Max Bercutt re: publicity for Hammer novel. C., 8/1/62
  - No. of guests for preview., 5/28/63; 3" × 5". (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Special screening list for cast and crew. C., 5/28/63; 3 pgs.
  - Official WB Guest Button-invitational Press Premier in Jackson Hole., ND (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Folder 1
  - Location information sheet. M., 6/21/62; 2 copies. 2 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Movement list. M., 6/21/62; 2 copies. 10 pgs.
  - Locations and description of scenes in continuity. Original and carbon., ND; 5 pgs. each. (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Possible pre- and post-production work to be done. Original and C., ND; 4 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Test scene for Minnie Cora. C., 6/13/62; 3 copies. 3 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Men's Wardrobe plots. M., 6/15/62; 51 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Women's Wardrobe plots. M., 6/15/62; 24 pgs. (Box 65, Folder 31)
- Folder 2
  - Staff and cast list with addresses and telephone numbers with FPpNAD., 6/22/62; 3 copies.m 4 pgs. each. (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - AN Catherine to HF re: correction of Frank to Fred Marlow., ND; 3" × 5".
  - Hoyt Bowers to Dept. Heads re: casting of Spencer's Mountain with correction., 6/26/62
  - Hoyt Bowers to Dept. heads re: names correction., 7/9/62; 8vo.
  - Cast stop and start dates. M., ND (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Screen tests for Spencer children parts. original and C., 6/20/62; 2 pgs.